Arrays can contain primitives and cart or et cetera, as well as object Norden on the primitive references
of a class, depending on the definition of that.
Think about every.
Like a building and building, the first floor is then this building called House in order to access
the house.
We are going to see the House of Index zero, House of Index one, House of Index two and House of Index
three.
Each element in the array is accessed via its index.
The index begins with zero and at and total array size minus one.
Okay, so this building is four four floors or four levels.
The last level is that the elements minus one or two, the total right size minus one.
All the elements of array can be accessed using Java for a loop or C loop or python.
OK.
In order to access this, a building like house number two in House two to access the third floor,
we write house and inside the house.
This is the name of ultracold house inside angled brackets following the name of the array.
We put the index of this array that we are going to access.
So in order to access the third floor, we put House and inside of the bracket we put the index of the
floor.
Now how to do this inside?
Got inside building.
We have public main, we are declaring an array of integer and allocating memory for five integers,
so at this level, Java will create or the system will create a reservation for inside memory, for
the array with five elements.
OK, see the code on the left and see the execution of it.
We need and realize the first element of the array.
So we've put array of zero equal to or equal to 10.
This means it will stores inside array of zero equal to 10 at index zero go and in and stolen it or
put inside that number that.
And is the second element or the rest of the elements?
Array of one equal to 20.
So go at index one in this array and put it inside at 20.
And so on, go to a rate at Index two and put 30, go at index three of this array and put forth the
go at Index four and put 15.
OK.
This is how we insert and how to initialize the elements now in order to access the elements of specific
array.
We have to make for a loop and this starts from zero.
The trade at length and the mod is A-plus Plus.
So the system that added print will print a arae at I.
This is the angle the brackets of I.
Angled to break every angle, the brackets, and I this is the key to make a loop through these elements.
So we are going to read all these animals, OK?